ajaxblender.com 2017-05-31

# Privacy Policy & NDA — ajaxBlender.com

## Privacy Policy

#### Introduction

ajaxBlender respects your privacy and intellectual property. Maintaining your privacy and confidentiality is of paramount importance to ajaxBlender, and we assure you that we will maintain and use your provided information responsibly.

We want to ensure your comfort in knowing that ajaxBlender keeps your information private and secure. We will collect and use information through our Web Site only in the ways disclosed in this document. This document applies solely to information collected from the Web Site of ajaxBlender. This legal document is an important part of our Web Site and our Terms of Service.

#### Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA)

Any information you provide to us at our Web site when you establish or update an account, (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, artwork, graphic files, intellectual property, etc), is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable ajaxBlender to deliver quality services and products to you. At no time will your information be shared with a third party.

ajaxBlender guarantees that all provided information will be kept confidential. Individual NDA contracts are available to ajaxBlender clients.

#### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.

#### General Browsing

We only will collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc.) that you voluntarily provide through our Web site or e-mail correspondence.

To improve our Web site and to better meet your needs, ajaxBlender also gathers navigational information about how you use our Web site. This information allows us to see which areas are most visited and helps us improve the quality of visitors’ online shopping experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our Web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).

#### Use of Cookies

To allow our server to “recognize” you when you visit our Web site in the future, ajaxBlender uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow ajaxBlender to make our site more responsive to your needs, by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and are used by ajaxBlender to help track your activity while visiting our Web site. In addition, ajaxBlender uses cookies to help keep track of support requests and to tell us whether you have previously visited our Web site. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site.

Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

#### Updating Personal Information

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information by logging into your account.

#### Use of Forums / Discussion Boards

None of the information contained on our Web site forums and discussion boards is medical, legal, business, or other advice or opinion of ajaxBlender.

Any opinion expressed via this service is that of its author. Users are reminded that postings are automatic, instantaneous, and may or may not be moderated prior to publishing. Additional facts and information on legal or other developments may affect the subjects discussed. Confidential information should not be discussed. ajaxBlender assumes no responsibility for the content or consequences, direct or indirect, of communications by users.

#### Newsletters and Promotional E-mails

ajaxBlender may periodically offer free newsletters and promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. We will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current specials and deals. You may “opt-out,” or unsubscribe from our newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements by following any unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail, newsletter or personalized on-line advertisement you receive from us. After doing so, if you have opted out of receiving all newsletters or all promotional emails, you will not receive future promotional emails or newsletters, unless you open a new account, enter a contest, or otherwise subsequently sign up to receive newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements. Please Note: If you agree to receive e-mails from any of our third party service providers or any third party merchants on our site, you will receive e-mails separately from them, and information that you choose to disclose to them will be subject to their privacy policy. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive their e-mails, you will need to follow their own specific opt-out instructions, as opting out from ajaxBlender as described above will not opt you out of their promotional emails.

#### Links

For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other sites. ajaxBlender is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Data Storage and Security

ajaxBlender protects user information with the following security measures: secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy.

#### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to keep your privacy confidential, we may be forced by law to give information you have provided to us for our services. We may also give information against someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as fraud). In addition, it may be necessary for us to provide customer information to third parties, such as credit card  
companies, for the purpose of resolving disputes that arise in the normal course of business.

#### Questions/Changes in Policy

If you have questions or concerns with respect to our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. ajaxBlender reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless stated otherwise.

If elements of this document change, we will post the policy changes in on this Web site. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about our policies, products and services.

You may also contact us regarding any questions about this document, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site via postal mail by sending a letter to:

Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer  
ajaxBlender.com  
c/o MediaWorks 7, LLC  
2224 Dividend Drive  
Columbus, OH 43228

#### Effective Date

The Privacy Policy and Non-Disclosure Agreement are effective as of July 7, 2007 and last updated on Ocrober 7, 2009.
